ccbg.com 2011-11-22

# 

                                                                                                                    Rev. June 2010
                          WHAT DOES CAPITAL CITY BANK GROUP DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL
 FACTS                    INFORMATION?
                          Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
 Why?                     consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how
                          we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                          understand what we do.
 What?                    The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                          have with us. This information can include:
                               Social Security number, income, credit history and credit scores
                               Account balances and payment history
                          When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this
                          notice.
 How?                     All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday
                          business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                          customers’ personal information; the reasons Capital City Bank Group chooses to share; and
                          whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                   Does Capital City Bank
 Reasons we can share your personal information                                                Can you limit this sharing?
                                                                        Group share?
 For our everyday business purposes—
 such as to process your transactions, maintain
                                                                            Yes                              No
 your account(s), respond to court orders and legal
 investigations, or report to credit bureaus
 For our marketing purposes—
                                                                            Yes                              Yes
 to offer our products and services to you
 For joint marketing with other financial companies                         Yes                              Yes
 For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
 information about your transactions and experiences
                                                                                                            *Yes
                                                                            Yes
  *Sharing of information cannot be limited to our
  affiliate Capital City Services Company.
 For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                            Yes                              Yes
 information about your creditworthiness
 For our affiliates to market to you                                        Yes                              Yes
 For nonaffiliates to market to you                                         Yes                              Yes
                               Visit any Capital City Bank office or
 To limit
                               Call our Client Service Center at 888.671.0400
 our sharing
                           Please note: If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from
                           the date we provide this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share
                           your information as described in this notice. You can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?                Visit any Capital City Bank office, call 888.671.0400 or go to www.ccbg.com.

Page 2
Who we are
Who is providing this              Capital City Bank Group includes Capital City Bank, Capital City Services Company,
notice?                            Capital City Trust Company and Capital City Banc Investments.
What we do
How does Capital City Bank         We restrict access to nonpublic information about you to those employees who need
Group protect my personal          to know that information to provide products and services to you. We also maintain
information?                       physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal laws to
                                   guard your information.
How does Capital City Bank         We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Group collect my personal               Open an account, deposit money, use your debit card or credit card
information?                            Pay your bills or apply for a loan
                                  We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus,
                                  affiliates or other companies.
                                   Federal law gives you the right to limit only
Why can’t I limit
all sharing?                            sharing for affiliates’ business purposes—information about your
                                         creditworthiness
                                        affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                        sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                   State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
                                  Your preference will apply to any account on which you have sole signature authority.
What happens when I
limit sharing for an              Your opt-out preference will remain in effect until revoked by you.
account I hold jointly with
someone else?
Definitions
Affiliates            Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial
                      companies.
                         Capital City Bank
                         Capital City Services Company
                         Capital City Trust Company
                         Capital City Banc Investments
Nonaffiliates         Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial
                      companies.
                         Nonaffiliates we share with can include companies such as mortgage companies, insurance
                          companies, check printing companies and others.
                    Information is shared with nonaffiliates only when:
                         1. Necessary to provide services required to maintain your accounts or complete
                             transactions you have initiated or
                         2. Mandated or permitted by law or
                         3. Required in the event of a national emergency.
Joint marketing       A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial
                      products or services to you.
                         Our joint marketing partners include Elan, Elavon and Invest Financial Corporation.
